

CHARLES JASON ALBELDA Graphic Designer

About Me

Hello, Good Evening, my name is Charles Jason Albelda, I'm 20 years old and I recently studied at Davao Del Norte State Colleges. And my course is Bachelor of Science in Information Technologies, and I am in my 4th year of college in this opening school year, and now I am focusing on Graphic design, Photographer and Videographer. I have 4 years' experience in graphic design, and I recently worked in Advertising, and my role in that job is graphic design and I work designing banners, birthday tarpaulins, flyers, brochures.

My Contact

- <u>albeldacharles@gmail.com</u>
- **(**) 09153985743
- Purok 2, New Malitbog, Panabo City

Hard Skill

- Creativity
- Visual Communication
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- · Print and Digital Design Knowledge

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- · Hard Working

Education Background

- Primary : Rodrigo D. Mabitad
 Sr. Elem. School Purok 2, New Malitbog,
 Panabo City (S.Y. 2013-2014)
- Secondary : Panabo Sda
 LearningCenter Inc. Purok 18, New Visayas,
 Panabo City (S.Y 2017-2018)
- Senior High : MaryknollCollege of Panabolnc. Purok Atis, Sto. Niño, Panabo City(S.Y 2019-2020)
- College : Davao Del Norte State CollegeNew Visayas, PanaboCity Third Year College (BSIT) (S.Y 2022-2023)

Objective

I am Seeking for a company,where I can develop myself fully and joyfully give out my best of my skills,experience, and talentsto become its strong assets.

Work Experience

PCWORKS ADVERTISING PANABO CITY

Pc Works Panabo
OJT Graphic Designer
(2019-2020) (2020 - 2023)

Freelance Graphic Designer (2019 - Present)